gathersuccess.com 2019-05-19

# Disclosure, GDPR , PDPA & Privacy Policy | GatherSuccess

At Buyza, we are committed to ensure we are compliance with GDPR. We believe in making our terms for marketing to be concise, transparent, intelligible and easily accessible on all our websites. They are written in clear and plain english and every information collected through forms online is never been used to be sold to other but for the sole purpose or providing products or services or information that the user request on our websites. In the page below explains how information collected is used.

At Buyza, we are committed to ensure the appropriate handling and protection of your personal data and privacy in accordance with Singapore’s Personal Data Protection Act 2012. Buyza is managed and owned by Buyza Pte Ltd.

 **Terms and Conditions for Consent to Marketing Information and Personal Data Usage**

If you wish to withdraw your consent, please email to peter@Buyza.com with your name and email address and contact number , it will take 2 to 7 workings to process with a response that you will be removed to be confirm.

This blog is a sponsored blog created or supported by a company, organization or group of organizations. For questions about this blog, please contact Phang Alvin.  
This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made in this blog. All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third party ad network. Those advertisements will be identified as paid advertisements.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.  
To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org

This blog does contain affiliate links and sponsored links which will provide commission to the writer of the content.

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, Open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

**•** To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

**•** To improve our website in order to better serve you.

**•** To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

**•** To quickly process your transactions.

**How do we protect your information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

We do not use an SSL certificate

**•** We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like names, email addresses, or credit card numbers.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**

**•** Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.

**•** Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.

**•** Keep track of advertisements.

**•** Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won’t affect the user’s experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

However, you will still be able to place orders .

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

**•** Remarketing with Google AdSense

**•** Google Display Network Impression Reporting

**•**  Remarketing in Facebook Marketing

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out: **  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.****

******  
********California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

**According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

**•** On our Privacy Policy Page

Can change your personal information:

**•** By emailing us

**•** By logging in to your account

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify you via email

**•** Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

**•** Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

**•** Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.

**•** Send you additional information related to your product and/or service

**•** Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**

**•** Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

**•** Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

**•** Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

**•** Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

**•** Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

**•** Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**

**•** Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

****and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.****

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
